<resources>
    <string name="app_name">InteractiveStory</string>
    <string name="merchant_and_the_genie">Merchant and the Genie</string>
    <string name="aladinStory">Once upon a time, there was a poor boy named Aladdin who lived with his mother.
        One day, a rich stranger came to their house looking for Aladdin.
        ‘I am a merchant,’ he told Aladdin’s mother.
        ‘I have come all the way from Arabia.
        I want to take your boy with me for a little work,
        but I will pay him so much that you will not be poor anymore.’</string>
    <string name="merchantStory">
        Sire, there was once upon a time a merchant who possessed great wealth, in land and merchandise, as well as in ready money. He was obliged from time to time to take journeys to arrange his affairs. One day, having to go a long way from home,
        he mounted his horse, taking with him a small wallet in which he had put a few biscuits and dates,
        because he had to pass through the desert where no food was to be got.

    </string>
    <string name="dogStory">Long time back, ours was a happy and prosperous family.
        We were three brothers who loved each other very much. In due time, our old father became very ill.
        He left for heaven and willed each of us a thousand gold dinars.
        We were clever so we invested in various shops and soon became well-to-do merchants.One day my eldest brother had the idea of expanding his trade connections in other kingdoms.
         </string>
    <string name="kingStory">A young king’s wife was cheating on her husband with a slave paramour.
        When the king found out, he mortally wounded the slave.  It turned out that the king’s wife was an enchantress, and she put a spell on her lover to keep him alive.
        In revenge, she cast a spell on her king husband, making him half man and half marble, and turned his fishing kingdom into a desert and lake. </string>

    <string name="hunchStory">In Casgar, on the utmost boundary of Tartary, lived a tailor and his pretty wife.
        One day a little hunchback seated himself at the shop door and began to sing and play on a tabor.
        The tailor invited the hunchback in to entertain his wife.
        The hospitable wife immediately placed a dish of fish before the men.
        The hunchback swallows a bone and chokes to death. </string>
    <string name="horseStroy">The people were rejoicing in Shiraz, Persia.
        They were happily celebrating the feast of the New Year.
        That day the Sultan had arranged for great fairs and festivals in the main square of the city.
        The Sultan sat on his throne and watched his subjects celebrating.
        Just then the crowd stopped amidst their actions and looked surprised.
        They saw a man riding a wooden horse that was decorated with silk and jewels as a real horse.</string>
    <string name="aladdin_and_the_lamp">Aladdin and the Lamp</string>
    <string name="two_dogs_and_the_old_man">Two dogs and the Old Man</string>
    <string name="continue_reading">Continue Reading</string>
    <string name="the_merchant_and_n_the_genie">The Merchant and   the Genie</string>
</resources>
